on point and or if there's additional suggestions
that you may have, we obviously welcome that.
And then I think you know this as I was out,
but Chrissy and I did one yesterday, we put a deal in,
but most of the deals at this point are entered in.
You know, I think Chrissy and maybe you can speak
to sort of the accuracy from those inputs.
And so now we're kind of like, okay, what's next?
You know, we've got like a running list of tweaks
and changes that we noticed as we worked through that,
that we're gonna talk with you about
we obviously sent over.
So I think high level, that's sort of my,
you know, my assessment of where we're at,
but Chrissy and I also has been in this,
so I'd love Chrissy in for you to share too.
Yeah, I mean, I think what you said
is very accurate, high level overview.
And then I think Ray and I think Gustavo,
you were on some of the calls with Zach and I
last week when we were in the midst of all the auditing
after the team built them, very close.
I think I have just one more to build today
and then the 26 deals will be complete.
So like Nate said, I think as soon as that Amazon
OVG one is done, then I think we can really
start cleaning up.
There are some like random second 20, 26 deals.
I noticed some of those things.
So I think we tried to put that feedback together
in the Excel document that I sent over yesterday.
I know we shared that before and then Zach
tried to help us prioritize some of those things.
Yeah, I sent a note to Gustavo earlier.
So I know we're working through your Excel list.
So, you know, the easy stuff is the account
opportunity cleanup that's pretty simple on our end.
We will look into the deal totals.
I know, like it's funny how every time we troubleshoot
it seems like it's calculating,
but we will do a hot it now that like everything's
mostly complete and make sure all the totals
are adding up.
So we'll take that on.
I think some of the other stuff we will,
I haven't had a chance to like dive into
too much detail yet, but I know Gustavo
and I will kind of dive into those.
So the training material, that's pretty easy.
We can get that up and running.
Maybe once we kind of like finalize
and get some of these things built out,
but we can definitely see that.
That's nice, thank you.
Yeah, I guess just anecdotally
why you guys have been doing deals over the last week.
You used to more so steam like process wise,
like everything sort of mostly makes sense.
You know, even if there are a few hiccups
or a few things you want to tweak.
Yeah, I think so.
I was telling Nate when we were going
through the training yesterday.
Sorry, I'm looking at my other screen
because I have it on my big monitor.
I think a lot of it is like learning how the system works
and like where you can click and edit and where you can't
and going back and forth between like the general page
and then like the deal lines page.
And then I also showed him how to export deal lines.
So that was our like quick way to check math.
Yep, we can try to make it to where it shows totals.
But yeah, exporting is definitely the way to go
as far as just kind of confirming for sure.
Yeah, I mentioned last week, I think the total,
I think it is moving, but I think once you start adding
like eight line items in 60 seconds,
I feel like that's where it may be legs.
So like once I was starting to audit
and really get going, I was moving quickly.
So that's why I'm wondering
if it just wasn't catching up in time.
Yeah, we'll take a look at that.
I'm sure we can get that calculating faster
or refreshing faster or something like that.
Okay.
Well, that's good.
I think here's, I guess what I see is like the inventory,
I think now is mostly in place.
And as I mentioned, I think while Zach was here,
but Nate, you are out is now anytime we wanna make changes,
let's use this inventory that's been like imported
as like the master rate card.
Cause I think the issue previously was that,
three different sets of inventory sources in a way,
there was like the sort of like a master spreadsheet,
but there was also what's in track.
And then there was the price grids, I think we're calling
them and the nomenclature probably didn't match
sort of across all of them.
And I think now if we can sort of use the inventory
for the 2026 in particular,
and then when we roll it over to 2027,
let's make the changes there,
or at least export from Dynamics
so that we're sort of keeping everything in line
and we can import updates in bulk maybe
or wherever you guys don't say this.
Sorry about that.
So I think like if we can keep them all in line,
like all the issues like I think we had in the last month
or so where like what was in track just didn't line up
with how you guys were actually maybe like putting them
into the contracts and stuff.
I think that'll like resolve things in the future.
So does that make sense?
And that you agree while you're on your side?
I wonder, I think it would be helpful to start high level
with the document that Christine sent over
around just the project roadmap.
Maybe we can just pull that up and talk through that.
And Christine, do they have editing access to that?
Did we send it in a way that we can share it in that way
or?
I didn't share it in that way.
I mean, if maybe if Ray makes any edits
we can make it a shared doc.
I think I just attached it to the email.
Yeah, I mean, I would say if you can feel free
to red line it Ray or add things in,
but why don't we talk through this,
would love to see if there's any gaps
from your perspective on the leapside.
And then to the extent we have time,
maybe we get into some of the, you know,
the Excel sheet where we had kind of very drill down
feedback on specific items.
Yeah, let's talk through it.
I glance through it.
I think, you know, for the most part,
everything made a lot of sense, but let's chat through.
I think for the purposes of where we're at, you know,
like it sounds like the closed one
or the stuff that's already been sold
is mostly in a good spot.
Maybe it sounds like mine is one deal.
It sounds like I think it's where now
we just have to maybe make sure that the pipeline stuff
probably mirrors and matches the correct inventory
now that that was rebuilt in the last, you know,
two, three weeks or whatever.
So I probably agree with this assessment,
but really to close one stuff,
I think it's closer to 95 or, you know,
something like that.
As far as like the packages,
I know you might have some feedback,
Christine, on this.
Barry any changes we make there.
I think the functionalities there
and the packages are mostly built,
but you guys probably, as you were going through,
had to build some new packages
or just update a few things.
But for the most part,
I think packages and inventory have been mostly built out.
I think you guys have done some training on this,
but we're happy to also do like another one-off training.
I know like in the last week or so
it was a bit of a scramble
just to kind of like,
let's just get everything going before Zach was out,
but we're happy to help do that.
We're seeing on that,
just sticking with that note real quick.
I mean, obviously it was not there for Zach's training.
You know, and I had previously
when we built functionality out, built the deal.
I don't think it's overly complicated.
I mean, there are a lot of things you gotta fill out
to get to the point where you're building the deal,
but I think you guys have done a pretty good job
of making it clear on like what fields need to be filled in
versus what don't.
And I will say I found it relatively easy
to put deal lines in.
I think interestingly, you know,
the way that they're showing up,
and this maybe gets a little more nitpicky,
but there's probably some suggestions
we might have or tweaks we might wanna make some of it,
potentially could be tweaks
to how we think about naming conventions,
but also we noticed the notes weren't in there.
You know, the deals don't total
and then one thing that I personally find
to be very annoying is that once a deal is built
within a deal, you can't see all the items
within the deal in one place.
You have to like click over within Dynamics
and it would be much more efficient
to be able to just see everything that's in their deal
because often you wanna look at things
in comparison in that way.
And sorry, I didn't mean to like, I just kinda did it.
I didn't mean to like start getting into the weeds.
No, that's good feedback.
I know like, oh, this isn't a good example,
but it'll only show like total, like a few here
and you gotta put some-
Yeah, like four, I don't know, four-ish line items.
You have to go into the next page in the next page.
Yeah, that's like, that's not a great way
to be able to view what's in their deal.
We'll see if we can expand how many can show here,
otherwise we'll try to come up with another way
to visualize or show what's added.
Great, yeah, and then totaling it too is another thing.
Like even when you download, you know, the sheet,
you still have to add a total column.
Like that's a big part of how we wanna look at this
is how the inventory totals up.
And I'm sure it obviously shows up in a different place,
but not within the deal builder.
Yeah, I think we have it for packages.
We'll try to move it over
when you're doing individual line items.
So that one's probably one Gustavo,
we could probably replicate there as well.
Yeah, Nate, when, if you're looking at a package,
we didn't look at a package yesterday,
but if you see down at the bottom,
well, once you add in a package, it shows the price.
And then as you start to add things
or change rates, those numbers will update.
So that's really nice for the package itself.
Move that over to the inventory style, I would imagine.
Yeah, so the packages,
do they currently not exist within
when you go to browse inventory,
you actually have to browse packages separately?
Yeah, because it's,
because we're trying to like have it pick a package
and then show all the items underneath it,
sort of built in where you add it through the browse package.
But it will show you the totals.
And I think we have it sort of going off
what the Raycard price is telling you
like what the difference is.
But once you start changing these prices here or editing,
then you'll see the totals update and all that.
But I do think we can make some tweaks there.
And if you had any of these here,
we'll try to make sure we note it or add it to here
based on what we've shared through today.
Okay.
Christine, do you think additional training
on building deal construction is needed?
I feel like we should ask the team that.
Okay.
Yeah, I've been to in it, so I know how to do it.
I'm the wrong person to ask, I think.
Okay.
You're a pro now.
Yeah, let us know.
I mean, we can, we talked about it in email the other day,
but the Thursday call,
I think they dropped off at the end of July,
but we can throw that back on if you guys wanna have
just like some one-off sessions for an hour
or we could just schedule it one-off any time.
So just put us in.
Okay.
I think it would be helpful maybe for us to have
one one-hour call a week right now
as opposed to two separate calls.
Sure.
I always have, today I don't,
but I typically have a call right after this,
so we either can go back to the Thursday time
or I can send you some other times that work for us
and for an hour block and you let us know it works.
And then we just.
Yeah, well, remind me,
what was our Thursday time that we originally had?
One, sorry, let me look, I'll tell my head.
Is it noon?
It was three p.m. Eastern.
Oh yeah, noon.
Is it any time?
I mean, my guess is Christine,
tell me if this was accurate for you two,
because we had had that blocked,
I'm guessing I don't have much booked on Thursdays at noon now
because that time was saved for you guys.
So, I mean, it'd probably just be easiest
to go right back to that.
Yeah.
That sense.
I'll update the Friday invite to just go back
to be on Thursdays now.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
And we can do one offsets needed to your point.
Okay, so we'll check in with the team on training,
building into auditing deals.
I feel like that's sort of the stage
that we're currently in,
although Christine did a lot of the auditing work
last week, so we're probably now
to that number four here, right?
I think for the most part,
we deleted all the line items off of everything
because we had to rebuild the inventory.
So any deals out there,
I'm sure you guys rebuilt or put in the close one deals.
I think the only thing maybe we need to audit
are any deals that are out there
that don't currently have a line item on it.
Do you wanna like keep those
or those pipeline ones that we now need to put
new potential open pitches to, you know,
that type of thing,
just because we had to clear everything out
with the new inventory.
Does that make sense?
You're saying anybody who had built something
in the pipeline would have been erased.
Am I understanding that correctly?
Yeah, I think we decided on the calls
that like there was no way to sort of keep the inventory
that was on there.
So it's better just to delete the deal lines,
rebuild the inventory,
and then we'd have to re-add deal lines
to any of the pipeline items or pipeline deals.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, that makes sense.
I think a lot of our, yes, no problem,
I think we just need to communicate that
with the sales team, obviously,
that anything that's currently in the pipeline
just needs to be rebuilt.
Yeah, we can probably find any deals without deal lines
and then send a list over and you guys can tell us
if you want to delete those or if Tiffany
or whoever wants to add new lines back to them.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
And then on all the existing deals that are closed one,
how do we just pull up a report to just look at those?
Collectively.
Yeah, I think we have closed one.
Also, yeah, right, I'm sent in the chat.
While we were doing the audit,
we kept everything as like prospect identified
for all the deals.
Oh, that's right.
We need to flip them back to close one.
That's why I think so.
Yeah.
So I think most of them can be moved back to close one.
I think most of them can be moved back to close one.
Some of them can be moved to closed one.
So I don't know if that's something you want me to do
to make sure it's all the current partners
get shifted to closed one or if you guys want to do that.
How about I'll flip you a list and you confirm
these are the ones that are all set
and we can flip the closed one.
Okay, that sounds good.
And that's when we flip it to close one,
this view I think is open for you guys,
it'll populate.
I'm sure if I made this like...
Yeah, could you change it to prospect identified maybe?
Just temporarily you'll see like these are some of the deals,
but we will definitely close out, close them as one
and then this will,
you don't have to manually update any of these.
This one should be anything regardless of stage for 2026.
We'll clean up some of these views,
maybe after we finalize some of the stage updates
and confirm a few things on your end.
And Christine, my thought on this was perhaps
we've done this before with other reporting functions
to confirm revenue numbers is maybe you and I
just use that list and verify that,
how we're tracking the total revenue for a deal
aligns with exactly what's there
before we published a track or pushed a track.
I think that's a good idea because I mean,
I was the one doing most of the auditing.
I told Zach to work on his other stuff
so he could be more efficient.
So I mean, obviously there could be some human error.
So I think checking those total revs
at least will be good and good find.
We'll go through also verify the total as well.
Great.
To your point on the track integration,
I think everything we've built should sink over.
I think it's more a matter of connecting with Cameron
when we feel like the current deals that are there
are in a good spot and maybe just have them
do one more test or something
just because it's been a little while
since we did the tests.
It was successful.
I think the last time we did like a single test record
but we can connect Cameron once we kind of
just finalize a few of these items.
And can you remind me, do you guys have access to track?
Like admin, you could sign in.
Okay.
And I actually, I figured out
how to export some of the things from there.
I know you'd sent us previously
so I was just kind of verifying a few things
I think a couple of weeks ago.
So, but you actually were able to see it.
I think the one reminder though
is that for these closed one deals
because we're creating brand new inventory
they're gonna get another deal in track.
And I think you will make that one maybe not visible
or maybe just hard for now.
But in the future, when we roll over a 2027 deal
for anybody that's like maybe multi-year
or you sell somebody new,
you should just have one deal in track
hopefully going forward
and then it has the right inventory and so on.
Yep.
And we have to actively publish a deal
for them to see externally.
So we just won't publish the ones
that come in from Dynamics.
Perfect.
I think once we turn the track integration on
maybe it's worth like we set up a call
just to kind of look throughout
how everything is on your end in track.
That sounds good.
Yeah.
And I know one of the things on our list
was the external and internal descriptions
which I realized somehow that note
was copied and pasted with another one
but the internal and external.
Let's see.
So it should be line
which one is it?
Line seven.
It says add rate card descriptions,
the actual description and column B.
It looks like we just accidentally copied
and pasted over.
So then-
I think actually,
Gustavo, we've already talked about
the internal external descriptions.
I think that was the weaker too, right?
Yeah, so we may have already made
some of those changes.
We just need to surface the fields
in the deal line builder or something.
Okay.
So I was gonna say that's one that we can check
when we do the track audit,
like how did it work?
Where just the external facing notes went to track.
That's a good call.
The internal facing ones are like
the Wasserman valuation type info
and like how we sell it.
That's actually why I exported the inventory from track
because I wanted to see what that description field
was there.
I think if we just create
another random description field in Dynamics,
it's not gonna sink over
because we haven't created that field on that side.
So that's the hope.
And soon when we map it correctly,
then I think it would all work properly.
So.
All right, so that's this.
I think I've had some thoughts actually
on this multi-year and playoffs and so on.
So for the multi-year,
I wanted to run something by you guys.
I know we have the automation
that if you put the term as three years
or more than one that we have an automation
that would create the deals in the future years.
But I'm wondering if you guys have so many changes
year to year that you wanna only roll them over
when you're ready to
and we kick off a process that anybody that had 2026
and more than one year on the term,
we roll it over when you guys feel comfortable
that inventory is correct or something like that.
I just wanted to kind of throw that out.
We can have the automated process,
but I just know you guys are undergoing changes
to what is offered and inventory and things like that.
Pretty often there are these packages set up.
If it's set once it's sold and it's a multi-year deal
and you wanna automate it,
we can definitely turn that back on.
But I just wanted to throw that option out there.
I'm not sure I'm completely following this,
the recommendation or suggestion you're making, right?
Can you, can you say?
Yeah, so for like 2026 deals,
we were putting them in.
And if they had a term of more than one year,
we've turned off the automation
that would have created the 2027 and beyond deals.
I was just wondering,
does it make sense to put,
turn that automation on and just have it replicate
these line items from the 2026 deal
and have the automation on as we had built it?
Or do you want to have like,
when you guys are ready and you feel comfortable,
anything that had a 2026 deal
that had a term of more than one,
let's roll over the 2027 inventory,
only because I think sometimes you guys are having
a lot more changes to the inventory
and different things going on.
So I just wanted to run that by you.
Does that make some sense?
I think so.
My recollection from my last conversation with Zach
and perhaps I don't know if you all had
additional conversations about the multi-year
was that we were publishing everything as 26
and then we would have to manually go back
and update the multi-year functionality for each deal.
Is that?
I think so because we were like redoing the inventory,
we turned it off because we just wanted to get 2026 deals
in a good spot.
Yeah.
So like the idea was to get the automated process
back on so that now if you sell a 2026 deal
or 2027 deal that has a more than one-year term
that it would automatically create the future of your deals.
So that was sort of the ideal scenario
but I'm just wondering if you guys have
so many changes going on that it's like problematic
where you'd have to delete deals later
or delete things and then have to re-add and so on.
Cause I think deletions and dynamics
don't fully sink over to track.
It's really only modifications or ads, I believe.
I mean, ultimately, yes, we want the functionality
to moving forward, right?
From here on out, you close the deal, it's a multi-year
deal, you want it.
We do want that functionality within Dynamics
that it's gonna publish.
I think just to clarify my question was
we still need to go back with all the closed one
and add the multi-year details in, right?
3%, 5%, whatever, that's still the thing
that what Christine and I need to do
or is that something you all do?
Well, I don't know if we have the details through it
but if we do, we can trigger it
to create then the future of your deals, right?
We just need to know which ones of those deals
on the opportunity level.
I think we put the term and some of those escalators
and things like that.
That's where we'll need to update those
if they're not already updated.
Does that make sense?
And then we can help trigger it
so you don't have to manually create the 20, 27 deals
or 28 and so on.
I think that we should keep with the automation
to go into future years.
Like Nate said, I think that's the priority
and I think track and making sure that's accurate
is second priority.
And Nate, he's talking about if we make changes,
like if somebody swaps things out during the off season
and like we created an amendment or something.
Yeah, and that does happen obviously from time to time.
And I think that either way that's gonna necessitate
the account manager or the salesperson going in
and like editing the future year deal, right?
Yeah, in those cases it might be where you have to
do it on both sides.
That's the only time we're deleting something
you have to do it on both sides.
I mean, I think advantage.
I think the future outlook is more important.
Yeah, I agree.
So once we get step one here, phase one really dialed in,
it seems like that next step then is
to add the contract terms
and the multi-year functionality in for all of those deals.
And then one thing I'm not seeing on here
that I know has been discussed is incremental games
and how we're accounting for those
which took place this year in 26.
How is that reflected in the deal build
and the multi-year functionality and all that?
Yeah, you can correct me if I'm wrong.
Does the new inventory reflect on almost per game basis?
Right, say that again.
Like your new rate card,
it's kind of on a per game basis now.
Like previously it was on like a season long basis, right?
Yeah.
It's faked into the rate card
if you have the inventories based on number of games.
So if 2027 just had,
I think you guys are expanding games next year, right?
Yeah, we're going to 50, yeah.
So I think just the 2027 rate card
might have more inventory available
and that's how we adjust for what there is.
We didn't put, I don't think there's something saying
like you sold it for this very specific game.
Yeah.
But it is reflective.
I think in the new inventory
is how I understood it potentially.
And if I'm wrong, I could be, you know, let me know.
Well, I think what you're saying makes sense
and I believe you are correct in that.
I think we were,
I remember Zach not really being sure
how to account for it.
And I guess this may be a question
for us, Christine, to consider,
which is that, you know,
every year you've got the baseline deal
and then for the LEAP team, for your visibility,
the way this shows up within contracts,
is it's a non-amendment, it's an exhibit.
And so it basically says,
hey, you know, your baseline contract is it.
We're gonna deliver this thing for this many games
and in the future, if it grows,
here's what you're gonna have to pay for it.
Now, I would say that while we are kind of tracking
what our incremental game revenue is,
because it's important for us to be able to tribute
revenue to the growth of the league, right?
That's sort of a subset of a report that we would do.
I think the way it's set up,
how you just described it, right?
We wouldn't be able to do that.
But I think we need to determine how important that is
because it's more of an internal report versus like,
I mean, what we're always reporting it on for the most part
is like the holistic revenue of one deal
or the holistic revenue of the department
or all the deals together.
So this may be, Christine,
it might be a question for us to just think about like,
and from an account manager standpoint too, right?
Like think about the billing and how that's laid out.
Like we've got the billing built into the regular deal
and then there's a separate billing process.
It goes back to like finance and accounting
where they wouldn't be able to like,
if we're gonna, because ultimately we do want this
to inform them what they're gonna invoice partners.
They wouldn't be able to bifurcate those things
within a deal, right?
It would just be a total, but they would say,
okay, we gotta build someone that total.
And I think currently, Christine,
this is where I could use your help.
I think currently we're billing for incremental games
separately from the total
or are we combining those two when we send an invoice?
We've combined them.
Okay.
But I asked like, when we've done it.
Oh, sorry.
Go ahead, Ray.
I was gonna ask, if for next year,
are you going back to all the partners
and charging the additional few games worth for each?
Or is it now just their season long rate
gives them that many,
but new sales may have to account for more?
Does that make sense?
We, so if you send a deal two years ago,
you have an incremental games clause in your deal
and start it in, let's say, your deal rolls in next year.
Starting next year,
you will now be charged incrementally
versus like, I think what you're asking,
like Alexa Plus, we send Alexa Plus this year.
Actually, they have an incremental games clause too
in their multi-year.
So they signed on for whatever the quantity of games
was this year, but next year that's gonna grow.
So it's complicated.
I don't have an answer how to solve this.
Well, my thought is you could back into this in a way.
So like, if you now have 2027 rate card
that we build the inventory records for next year
that now reflect couple additional games
and more inventory,
but the price for the full season is different,
you could look at, for this client,
for this particular asset that you sold them,
they paid this much in 2026,
and then for 2027, they paid this much
and you could probably back out the escalator amount
and see this is how much incremental
it got you potentially.
Does that make sense?
It does, yeah.
Do you think that's a report
that we would be able to run within Dynamics?
I'm sure we can create some sort of way
to run the calculation
and then we would have it in a field
that you could put into a report.
And so just so I'm clear what you're saying
is in that scenario, you're running a report that says,
okay, in 27, their baseline deal was X.
And since it was a multi-year, their escalator was X.
So there's some incremental there.
And then, but the total deal
maybe shows a little bit more.
So then you would say, okay, well that's naturally
from incremental games.
I think that.
If that's a fair assumption or not.
And if it's not, I don't want you guys to report that
and say like.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just thinking like, are there other scenarios
that like an upsell, for example,
like if you upsold them, I guess you would have,
you'd have an amendment though
to say what the upsell was.
So I guess even in that scenario,
you should be able to say this was incremental.
I think we would compare one line item
from one year to the next.
And you could say excluding the escalator,
this is how much more or somehow less
if for some reason like it came out that way,
but you could show the difference,
the delta of what the partner is paying for that item.
It's mostly looking at it on the whole deal
because you may add new items
and that wouldn't give you the right.
It's interesting because when we,
so like I sort of think of this like taking the contract
as like the ultimate, you know,
it's like our Bible, it's how we know exactly
what's in their deal, what we're charging them, right?
Like I think the ideal scenario is that
when you build a deal,
because we pitched this way too.
So like when we put a poll's on front of someone,
you know, we start off saying,
hey, here's all the things
that we're gonna pitch you in your deal.
And as a WNBA grows and adds games
based on whatever is in your package,
like we may charge you for that, right?
Based on if it's executed or not or home and away,
like there's some different complexities there.
And then playoff, same thing, right?
So actually think of it kind of similar
to how we're building playoffs.
I think the ideal scenario
is that we'd have the ability
to add the incremental games inventory within Dynamics
to be able to then have that run separately.
Now it needs to obviously,
similar to however, playoffs is gonna show up.
I know we haven't built playoffs out yet, but,
and it's probably, I mean,
it's not a good thing we're not making playoffs,
but for this project, it makes it easier right now
because playoffs would be starting relatively soon.
But that's how I think is the best way to achieve it
because it's also gonna be way more clear,
I think for Christine and team
on like what specific benefits
need to be activated incrementally.
Cause otherwise Christine,
it just blends into the like holistic inventory
and it's gonna look like and track
that it's like a regular season thing
that you're supposed to deliver,
which it kind of is,
but it's actually due to the fact
that there's growing games.
Is it, you would want an incremental game,
or incremental game revenue line item on the deal,
but for every item in the deal?
Would you double the amount of the deal?
Well, you can only deliver, it's so nuanced
because certain inventory you can't deliver
for certain, like, you know,
there's also like national TV
versus local and local court, national court.
I mean, it's complex, but,
and so, you know, is every inventory,
there are some inventory items
that absolutely would be every game.
Like if you have season tickets
or I mean, really anything that you have
that we could deliver on an every game basis,
conceivably could be delivered for incremental games.
But then there's nuances to that
when you work with League rules
on a nationally televised game
versus a locally televised game, right?
So maybe it'd be helpful
if we sent you one of the more complex clauses
that we have that outlines incremental games.
Christine, I don't, maybe we can think about that,
but maybe you guys could just look at that
and read that and give you a better sense
for how it's, you know, how it's laid out.
But I think my vision would be,
and by the way, I'm open to other ways of doing this.
To me, it seems like it would be the cleanest
and most representative of a contract
in how we're doing deals is that within a deal,
you're building a deal and you're building out,
you know, in the 26th season,
when we close the deal now, it's like, great,
you know, here's the deal for 26.
When incremental games are added,
here are the benefits that are going to be associated
directly with those incremental games
and here's what that charge looks like in the future
and then playoff similarly, right?
Like with the build out playoffs
and then what benefits will be delivered for playoffs
and what the charge is for that.
Yeah.
I think that's the cleanest way to do it.
I mean, I don't know how on your end,
how that ends up like ultimately looking,
but like even Christine, just think about
how we built Alexa yesterday,
you know, we built the regular season
and there's an incremental games clause in their deal.
So then we would go and,
I don't know if it's like a new deal line or something,
like somehow it needs to still be affiliated
with the deal, right?
But we would then go and build out
the incremental games deal lines
and then the playoff deal lines.
I think in my head, the mechanics of it in dynamics,
we just need to figure out if it's
one flat incremental revenue line item that goes to the deal
or if it's on every line item
so that you can distinguish how much more you made
for this particular asset.
I guess that would be kind of like a question
I'm throwing back to you.
Is that something like you'll end up needing to do?
Yeah.
I mean, Christine, I think they're broken out
usually as like, if it's a package
that can continue versus like an individual element,
I think it would cause us to be
a little bit more detailed on the pricing of them
because it's possible that some of these incremental games
clauses might say like,
for every game we can deliver
one additional broadcast spot, I'm making this up,
one additional period and two additional tickets
to a game within the clause.
We might just say, therefore we charge you X per home game.
So that math was done on an Excel spreadsheet somewhere
but it wouldn't, what doesn't live in dynamics in that way.
So yeah, we would, it would be like pulling
individual inventory line items.
And there's, yeah, there's another layer of complexity
it was like it does add incremental inventory
but I think that floats back up to like the quantity
of games we can deliver each season, right?
At a high level, like that would automatically
expand the inventory.
Yes.
I think, I think we want to,
because I also don't want it to be where like,
you're doing double the line deal line items all the time.
So I want to think through the process a little bit.
So if you send any details you have,
maybe we can kind of stew on it a bit
and think about how this would be,
this would need to be tracked.
But it sounds like you do almost kind of need it
on a per line basis.
It may not be something you'll have to add every year
because obviously you're not adding games every year
but for next year, this would be applicable, so.
Yeah.
And to make it more complicated,
everybody's a little different
because the W keeps adding games.
So if you have like a longer contract,
you might have signed up with us when you,
when we had, you know, I'm just gonna make it up
but like 40 games and then you signed up this year,
you have 44 games and then, you know,
so next year goes to 50.
So some people are gonna have, you know, 10 extra games.
Some people have eight, some people have four.
Like it's, so we need to just make sure
that it accounts for the differences within a deal.
Like it's not gonna be equal for everybody
if that makes sense.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Record actively, like, I don't know
if it'll be as easy to like,
get all this calculated and into dynamics
but I think from 26 and forward,
we can definitely build that out
or figure out how to track that.
When was the last number of games changed?
Was it this year?
It was, I think, I think we've been flat
for two years now.
So is where are we at now, 46?
44.
44, yeah.
And I think, so three seasons ago, we were at 40.
Yeah.
And next year is like confirmed, we'll be at 50.
And I think there's a chance we could grow more.
It's so unique to the W, no other league does this.
It's so unique to the WNBI,
but it's like, you know,
how you grow the whole pie and everything.
I mean, it's a conversation that
partnership teams are having all the time
because it's like you signed these multi-year deals
that are locked in and all of a sudden,
we're adding eight games.
I mean, we have a partner right now
that signed a 10 year deal with us
during your like seven or eight.
And I mean, when we go to 50,
they're probably getting like 14 games for free
or something that's pretty crazy.
Yeah.
It is the first I've heard of it.
I mean, I know like,
NFO went to an extra regular season game
versus one less preseason,
but generally speaking, the number of games
is relatively flat elsewhere, I think.
Yeah.
It's unique to you guys,
a little bit more so than others.
Totally.
It requires quite an education process
for the prospect too,
because like if they're buying sports,
they'd never heard of this, you know?
So,
like what do you mean you're gonna charge us
even more the following year?
Makes sense.
I think we can think through the mechanics
of that one a little bit more,
but we have a few action items here,
I think as far as like getting you some lists of deals,
checking on the deal totals and so on,
and flipping, getting you a list of deals to flip
to close one,
I'll have you confirm that Christine,
and then we'll update some of the list views
and reporting if need be,
but those should start looking better once we do that.
Yeah, looking forward to it.
Yeah, I think we can get you something here, see.
And I'll finish up the final deal today.
So I think we'll be very close,
and we are very close right now.
I know we have this list,
so if we have any questions on it,
we'll let you know,
I know we've only sort of started digesting it
mostly today,
so if anything doesn't make sense, we'll reach out.
Cool, and Christine just confirming
the couple of things I mentioned,
like the deal line view
where we have to go to multiple pages,
is that on here?
Probably not, no.
I can get it added to manual here,
and I have a few other notes I'll make here.
Okay, great.
Yeah, and that totals thing too,
would be very nice if it totalled.
Yeah, 100%.
That one I know is probably easier to achieve.
I think the list at the bottom with all the deal lines,
I think we'll have to just work through that one
a little bit,
but we'll figure something out there.
Okay.
We're well over time, sorry.
No worries, luckily my next call,
10, 30 years on my guess,
just canceled SIP.
Oh, we got lucky.
Obviously if you're still building out any deals today
and have an issue, let us know.
We'll try to get some answers or info back to you,
but I think we're getting close to where
like the track integration will turn on soon.
We'll have to figure out some of the pipeline stuff,
but I think we can also help Tiffany and Bridget
get some of those in if they need,
or if they just need any guidance on it,
definitely let us know.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Cool.
Thanks, y'all.
Yeah, have a good weekend,
have fun on the trip.
Thanks.
We need to win, okay?
We need to win.
So put good vibes forward for a win for us.
Sending it your way.
All right, thanks, see you guys later.
Bye-bye.